(knocking on door)
- Is Pharrell here?
- I don't know whatchu talking 'bout.
- Neptunes presents the clones?
- All right, cool.
(hip hop beat plays)
♪ Sexy thing ♪
♪ (Girl your ass is so fat) ♪
♪ Been waiting to get wit' you ♪
♪ Hey yeah ♪
♪ Don't wanna sound
full of myself or rude ♪
♪ But you ain't looking at no
other dudes 'cause you love me ♪
♪ (I'm sorry baby, uh, so sexy) ♪
♪ So you think about a chance ♪
♪ You find yourself
trying to do my dance ♪
♪ Maybe 'cause you love
me (uh, you do it well) ♪
♪ So then we tried, I'm
thinking to slow down ♪
♪ Because you weren't used
to how fast we touched ♪
♪ (Fast we touched) ♪
♪ Then we locked eyes, and
I knew I was in there ♪
♪ And I was gon' tear ya
ass up (tear ya ass up) ♪
♪ I know that I'm carrying on,
never mind if I'm showing off ♪
♪ I was just frontin' (you
know I want ya babe) ♪
♪ I'm ready to bet it all,
unless you don't care at all ♪
♪ But you know I want ya (you
should stop frontin' babe) ♪
♪ Trying to be the best
girlfriend you could be ♪
♪ But still you sneak and look
at me, and girl I love it ♪
♪ Then you give your other girl a shove ♪
♪ Tell her you gonna
call her ask how it was ♪
♪ And she's gon love it
(whoa-oh whoa, yeah yeah) ♪
♪ So then we tried, I'm
thinking to slow down ♪
♪ Because you weren't used
to how fast we touched ♪
♪ (Fast we touched) ♪
♪ Then we locked eyes, and
I knew I was in there ♪
♪ And I was gon' tear ya
ass up (tear ya ass up) ♪
♪ I know that I'm carrying on,
never mind if I'm showing off ♪
♪ I was just frontin' (you
know I want ya babe) ♪
♪ I'm ready to bet it all,
unless you don't care at all ♪
♪ But you know I want ya (I want you) ♪
♪ (you should stop frontin' babe) ♪
♪ We got another one Pha-real ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ I call you Pha-real 'cause
you the truth, ha ha ♪
♪ Young great Hova ♪
♪ Uh (dance) yeah ♪
♪ lemme talk to 'em man ♪
♪ I'm a keep it real ♪
♪ Every time your name was brought up ♪
♪ I would act all nonchalant
in front of an audience ♪
♪ Like you was just another
shawty I put the naughty on ♪
♪ But uh, truth be told you
threw me for a loop, this Hov ♪
♪ I'm too old to be frontin'
when I'm feeling Denzel ♪
♪ And you acting like you
ain't appealing when you are ♪
♪ Stunting like you ain't
my only girl when you are ♪
♪ I'm ready to stop when you are ♪
♪ I know that I'm carrying on,
never mind if I'm showing off ♪
♪ I was just frontin' (you
know I want ya babe) ♪
♪ I'm ready to bet it all,
unless you don't care at all ♪
♪ But you know I want ya (you
should stop frontin' babe) ♪
♪ Oh, Dance, ooh ooh, whoa-oh, oh oh ♪
♪ Dance, ooh ooh, whoa-oh, oh oh ♪
♪ You like this Pharrell? ♪
♪ Thank you baby ♪
♪ Look ♪
♪ You leaving now, well
I'll see you later ♪
♪ I'mma slip through your window ♪
♪ Bye ♪
(drum beat fades out)